A handgun bullet travels at more than 700 miles per hour.
Hey, whoa. Absolutely not. No.
Look, if you don't wanna do it, you don't have to do it.
Okay. Good, I don't wanna do it.
Fine.
Goddamn! I'm alive.
Oh!
Oh, that's amazing!
I know, right. So...
Hmm.
Ready to go again?
Absolutely not.
Fine.
Don't just say "fine" and then shoot me in the chest.
'Cause it's not cool.
Like at all.
Okay. Jeez.
I always wondered why no one tried to be a superhero before me.
It turns out somebody had. Mindy Macready.
After her dad died,
his old partner on the force, Marcus, became her guardian.
-Is that a Pink Pony bag she's wearing?     -Nice backpack.
Thanks.
Steal it from a six year old?
Marcus dropped her off every day.
But as soon as he was gone, so was she.
No one at school found out
because she hacked into the server
and gave herself the award for perfect attendance.
Hit Girl and Big Daddy had been the real deal.
Mindy was gonna keep wearing the mask
as long as there were criminals to take down.
But no matter how many drug dealers she stopped,
she couldn't stop feeling alone.
Me? I'd given up being a superhero
because it was way too dangerous.
Only problem, I was dying of boredom.
Like most high school seniors,
I had no idea what I wanted to do with my life.
Hell, I didn't know what channel I wanted to watch.
It's just TV, Dave, not peace in the Middle East.
My best friends Todd and Marty
had no clue I was the first superhero to go public.
You guys watch Spider-Man last night?
Is it weird that Aunt May gets me kinda hard?
Not if you're a granny-slammer.
They may wear costumes, but it isn't Halloween.
They're real life superheroes,
and in the two years since the first ordinary citizens
donned capes and masks,
the movement has started to spread.
I became a superhero because of Kick-Ass.
Yeah, you just come home from work,
you grab your gear and you go out on patrol.
Help us make the streets safe.
I inspired all those people to get off their asses,
and now I was stuck on mine.
So that night after dinner,
I decided to get my old costume out.
-Sorry.     -Whoa! Can't you knock?
You know, buddy, it's perfectly normal for you to touch yourself...
Oh, Jesus, Dad. Get out!
If I was even thinking about a Kick-Ass sequel,
I had to get serious.
Hey. Hey, can we chat?
Please, Mindy?
Get in the cab. Meter's running.
I wanna team up like Batman and Robin.
Nobody wants to be Robin.
What's wrong with Robin?
Weren't you like Big Daddy's Robin?
Robin wishes he was me.
What I'm trying to say is we should be partners,
you and me, like the dynamic duo.
I'm in the NFL, Dave. You play pee-wee.
So? Train me.
I wanna walk the walk,
and you're the closest thing I know to a real superhero.
Aren't you tired of being on your own?
Don't you wanna know someone's there for you?
Someone who's got your back?
And you'll do anything I say?
Anything.
Hit me.
You're a 15-year-old girl.
What the hell?
Act like a bitch, get slapped like a bitch.
Oh, goddamn.
Mindy beat me like morning wood
every day for three weeks.
Come on. Guard up! Left, right, guard up!
Even with my damaged nerve endings,
it hurt like hell.
But, in a weird way, I kinda liked it.
It gave me a sense of purpose.
-What happened to your face?     -Nothing.
Like we were driving towards something.
Goddamn!
Oh! Oh, that's amazing!
All the other people putting on masks were just playing superhero.
We were training to really do it.
I couldn't tell my girlfriend Katie, or Marty and Todd.
But I didn't care. We were having too much fun.
Left, right, left!
Our own superhero team.
It was gonna be balls.
What the hell, Mom? Did you delete the news off the DVR?
Yes. Yes, I did, Christopher.
That was the one with Kick-Ass.
Oh, Christopher, you've gotta stop obsessing over this superhero.
He is not a superhero, Mom, he's a murderer.
He blew up Dad with a bazooka, for fuck's sake!
Your father died in a fire.
A fire? What is your problem?
You! You are my problem!
I am trying to raise you to be a normal boy!
That's why we moved to Long Island after your father's accident.
A bazooka is not an accident,
you delusional bitch!
This conversation is over.
Great. Then I'm leaving.
Come on, Javier, be cool.
Sorry, Chris, but your mom pays me not to be cool.
I hate you! You home-school me like I'm a prisoner!
You threw away my Red Mist costume.
God! I am not the problem! You are!
I wish you were dead!
Mommy?
Don't touch that.
Oh, I'm sorry. What is it?
It's a last resort. Like if all else fails and you're about to die.
Are you not scared to die?
Are you scared you're never gonna grow into your big boy pants?
I'm serious.
What if Spider-Man or Batman got killed one night? It could happen.
If you're scared of dying, one thing is certain,
you are going to die.
My daddy was never afraid of dying.
Look where that got him.
He knew he might have to make the ultimate sacrifice one day.
And that's why he made me promise
I'd never stop defending this city.
Cross my heart,
hope to die.
Your dad was insane. You know that, right?
You're wrong, Dave.
My daddy was the first real superhero,
not you or Red Mist. It was my daddy,
and it was an honor to serve by his side.
Hey, Min, how was school?
Super crazy.
Miss Mullins was out today, so we had Mr. Cooper teaching us biology,
such a grump.
Oh, really? That's weird because Principal Himoff called me yesterday.
You were supposed to get an award for perfect attendance,
but you didn't attend.
I followed you this morning. Saw you get into a cab with some boy,
and I lost you guys over the bridge.
So now you wanna tell me where you really were today?
I'm really sorry, Marcus. I didn't wanna make you mad.
Cut the waterworks, Min. You're 15, not five.
Okay.
Look, he asked me to cut class and go to the mall.
So, yeah, yeah, I did.
This has nothing to do with you being Hit Girl?
I'm not gonna find any ninja blades or throwing stars under your bed?
No. I just wanted him to like me. Okay?
Sweetie, no skipping school's not away to get boys to like you.
-I'm so stupid.     -Hey, hey.
You're one of the smartest little girls I know. Let's go get some pizza.
What, you mean I'm not grounded?
Well, just consider this awarning.
Hey, you sure you wanna give all your mom's things away?
What the hell am I supposed to do with all her stuff?
Damn, she had a nice pair of guns.
Dude, she's dead! Don't talk about her tits.
I was talking about these.
Oh, those. Those were my dad's.
Why don't you keep them?
Are you sure?
Yeah. I mean, they belong to you, right?
Come on, Chris. You're your own man now.
-Just be careful, all right?     -Yeah.
Whoa!
Definitely don't wanna keep those!
I'll take care of it.
You take the day off. Later.
Hey.
So, are you ready for your first field test?
What am I supposed to do with these?
Put them on and, uh, go fishing.
I'm the whitest pimp ever.
That's the idea. Take the next right.
Comes out on Flatbush.
You sure I should be doing this without my gear?
That's the point.
Kick-Ass isn't a costume. Kick-Ass is who you really are.
Dave Lizewski is the mask.
Well, my "mask" is about to get his teeth kicked in.
Hey, queer bait, where are you going with those bags, man?
Tell him you're on your way to fuck his mother with a 12-inch strap on.
I'm just taking a walk.
This really isn't what I do. I usually just call the cops.
Who are you talking to, man?
Uh, I'm just on a call. It was...
You know, service round here, it sucks, man.
Now give me the bags, faggot,
before I make you suck my fat cock, huh?
Come on.
Okay, Okay.
Can you believe I let Mindy beat the snot out of me for weeks
just so I could get my ass kicked again?
So much for a team.
You ready to die? You faggot!
You know, all that homophobic shit makes you sound super gay.
Come on, man. Come on.
If I ever catch you robbing again, shit-burger,
I'm gonna go Saudi Arabia on your ass and cut your hand off.
Promise me you're done with your life of crime.
I promise.
Pants on fire.
-What do you think?     -I think you almost got me killed!
No. What do you think of my line?
"Pants on fire." I wrote a whole bunch of 'em.
Run! I'll tell them you saved me. Go!
Female suspect fleeing Flatbush.
Under 5 feet. Masked. Armed with nunchucks and a sword.
-Hey, Min.     -Hey, Marcus. What's up?
I see you answered your phone.
That means you're not in school.
I was,
but I wasn't feeling so good, and so the nurse decided to send me home.
Poor thing. Well, I'm almost home.
I'll make soup and we can watch Jeopardy!
All righty. I'll see you soon, okay?
All right.
Shit!
You got my soup?
Let me take your temperature first.
Oh, you're really clammy.
I'll feel better after a nap-nap.
Close your eyes. I'm gonna get you that soup.
Is that blood?
Damn it, Mindy. I can't do this anymore.
Your father was like a brother to me.
He was a great cop and a hero.
But Big Daddy? That was not your father, okay?
That was someone who robbed you of your childhood.
And this?
Hit Girl? That's not who you are.
You are Mindy Macready and you're just starting high school.
I understand that you don't know who that person is yet,
but you will, you've just gotta try.
I don't want to.
You don't know what you want.
You can't. You're not an adult, not yet.
Yeah, well, I've done more in my 15 years than most adults have in their lifetime.
That note that your father gave you,
the one that you were supposed to open if anything ever happened.
What did it say?
That you would take care of me.
And that you were supposed to listen to me, right?
Well, listen up.
I want you in school. I want you to stop talking to that boy.
And I want you to promise me
that this is never gonna happen again.
Cross my heart,
hope to die.
Good.
Mindy!
What the hell?
First you almost get me killed, then you stand me up.
Dave, I'm sorry.
I mean, I... you are?
I am.
For everything.
Oh, okay, great.
I mean, "apologetic" isn't a word I'd use to describe you.
How many times do I have to say it?
Look, let's get out of here.
You gotta ease up. I think I might have broken a rib.
Dave, I'm done.
With training?
With everything.
Wait, you mean everything?
You can't. You're Hit Girl.
We were gonna start a team, you can't just quit.
This is who you are.
Not anymore, Dave.
I'm sorry, but it's over. I'm done.
She just broke up with him?
Just leave me alone.
Will you stop apologizing?
I don't know what's worse, that you're fucking a 9th-grader
-or that you just got dumped by one.     -Whoa, whoa!
Pedophile freak.
It's not like that.
Then what is it like? Please, tell me.
I can't. It's to do with the Kick-Ass thing.
I've got a secret for you. You remember Malik?
Dude who volunteers at your needle exchange?
His baton is so much bigger than Kick-Ass'.
-No.     -Yeah.
And by "baton," I mean penis.
Yeah, I got that. Thanks.
Fifteen gets you 20, pervert.
A freshman, Dave? You old, salty dog.
What's the problem? Grass on the field, play ball. Right?
No, Todd.
Chris, your tutor's here.
Chris!
Chris, your...
Holy shit. What the hell is that?
My destiny.
Chris, just because your mom liked to get a little freaky now.
I know what my role is in this, Javier.
My dad was a crime boss, so it just makes sense.
I'm a supervillain. It's evolution.
Come on, come on.
Just put those things down before you hurt somebody, Chris.
That's not my name.
Okay, okay. Uh, Red Mist...
Red Mist was my superhero name.
Henceforth I'll be known as
The Motherfucker.
After Mindy quit,
I decided to stop hitting the heavy bag and start hitting the streets.
Hey, Kick-Ass, welcome back!
-Yeah!     -Whoo!
You're the best, man!
Only problem, I was still on my own.
So I went online and found a physics professor
calling himself "Dr. Gravity."
Sure, he wasn't Hit Girl, but I had to start somewhere.
This is the zero G device that I invented.
Can levitate any object up to a ton.
For real?
Hell, no, man. This is a baseball bat wrapped in tinfoil.
But it fooled you.
Hey, could I get a Diet Mountain Dew, please?
I'm not even a physics professor.
Just a copywriter for an ad agency.
But that's why I love this stuff.
You can be anyone you want!
You done many team-ups before?
Kind of. Yeah. No, not really.
I was getting kinda nervous about being on my own, you know?
Yeah, me, too. I never even been in a fight.
Well, hopefully you won't have to.
I friended a guy talking about forming a team, if you're interested.
I don't know how serious he is,
but his picture was pretty hard core.
Are you kidding me? That's why I contacted you.
I didn't wanna freak you out by bringing it up too soon.
I'll show you his profile after I hit the men's room.
Your Uncle Ralph's not gonna be happy about this, Chris.
That's not my name.
I'm not calling you that, forget it.
Javier, you worked for my dad.
Then you worked for my mom. Now you work for me.
I'm probably the richest kid in New York City.
But if you don't like that, find yourself another motherfucking job, okay?
Yo, Kick-Ass!
Man, am I glad to see you.
Is there anything I can do to help, sir?
Yeah. I was hoping you can help me get a million hits on YouTube.
Come on. Come on.
Run, Kick-Ass, run!
Jersey Shore motherfucker!
Hey, what, you not interested in a fair fight?
That is no fair fight. Team meeting tomorrow.
I'll e-mail you the address.
Beware Dr. Gravity!
You had to admire the Doctor's enthusiasm.
I couldn't wait to meet his friends.
Hands in the air, Spring Roll.
Empty the register and don't do anything stupid.
Come on! Hey, where are your security cameras?
-We don't have them. Too expensive.     -Seriously?
What the fuck? How's this gonna go viral?
You want to be filmed?
Shut up and just get on the ground!
And you'd better tell people The Motherfucker was here.
What's wrong with you, boy?
Get on the floor, too, Gandalf,
or I will bust a cap in your ass.
You're gonna bust your own face when that gun kicks if you don't hold it properly.
Just get on the ground!
God, will you hurry up!
I told you.
Go! Go, go, go!
Start the car! Go, go!
It was amazing!
I feel so alive.
I know who I am. I know why I'm here.
I'm gonna fuck this world up!
They will know The Motherfucker's name!
You've gotta find me some bad-ass MMA types to train me, okay?
Like a Chuck Liddell or whoever.
Fuck, I don't care how much it costs.
I just wanna be able to kill Kick-Ass with my bare hands.
I gotta tweet about this.
All right. Are you ready?
Um, I don't know. Am I?
Yes, you are. You look great.
And Barbara's daughter, Brooke, is really nice.
What am I supposed to talk to them about?
I'd rather be water-boarded than listen to Justin Bieber.
-You're gonna be fine.     -I'm gonna be a disaster.
How do you know that?
Because it's a slumber party, for fuck's sake.
Dollar. Jar.
You're gonna need a bigger jar.
Pretty cool, huh? This is how the beer gets delivered.
Dude. You got a secret elevator to your underground headquarters.
Yeah. The guy I told you about owns this place.
It's like a real-life bat-cave.
-I know, right.     -Oh, yeah.
This is the single greatest thing I've ever seen.
Welcome to Justice Forever.
Hi, Detective Williams. This must be Mindy.
It is. Hi, Brooke.
You girls have fun and I'll pick you up in the morning, okay?
I'll be the one with the slit wrists.
No, you're gonna be the one that gets the awesome manicure.
-I am?     -Mmm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
Say "hey" to Mindy, ladies.
Hey.
I know you.
You're that freshman who took a ride on Dave Lizewski's disco stick.
I did not ride his...
If you just blew him, you're totes a virgin, right?
She didn't blow him, look at her.
Then what? Rim job? Hand job? Fingerbang?
Sweet-Ryan-Seacrest, you at least kissed him, right?
Totes.
You've never kissed a boy, have you?
Oh, my God, that is so adorable.
Maybe she's a dyke.
Maybe I'll jam my foot up your snatch.
Oh, she's super bitchy, I likes.
Then what's the big deal anyway?
What could be so great about gagging on some douche-bag's tongue?
It's pretty fucking great.
You know how you feel when you watch that video by Union J?
Holy shit, you don't know?
This will change your life.
♬ Don't ever say you're lonely Just lay your problems on me ♬
♬ and I'll be waiting there for you ♬
You guys love this shit more than fanboys love Stan Lee, don't you?
Who's Stan Lee?
♬ I'll carry you I'll carry you ♬
♬ I'll carry you ♬
♬ So you know that I'll carry you ♬
♬ Like you've been running for hours ♬
♬ And can't catch your breath ♬
♬ The demons are screaming so loud in your head ♬
♬ You're tired You're broken ♬
♬ You're cut and you're bruised ♬
♬ But nothing's too heavy Just hold on ♬
♬ I'll carry you ♬
What the fuck was that?
I know, right? I'm soaked.
That? That is who you are, Mindy.
You may not dress like us or talk like us,
but when it comes to boys, we're all the same.
Twilight. Channing Tatum. Union J.
It's biology, bitch. Don't fight it.
I, um...
I gotta go.
But we were gonna go and get high on bath salts at Logan's house.
Mindy, I wanna give you a chance that the rest of the girls in our class would kill for.
Don't you wanna walk out the door every day in skin-tight clothes
knowing that everyone worships you?
Don't you wanna sneak out at night, raise a little hell,
and show the world what a strong,
independent woman is capable of?
Don't you wanna belong?
♬ So you know that I'll carry you ♬
Can I wear this to Logan's?
Yay!
It's gonna be so much fun.
So we tried the cops and tried the newspapers,
and even set up a, you know, a thing on the Internet
for people to help us find Tommy.
Um...
But we got nothing. We never saw our son again.
I came up with the name Remembering Tommy,
and, uh, we've been doing this three nights a week. So...
Colonel Stars and Stripes found us online.
That's terrible, guys. I'm real sorry.
I became Night Bitch after my sister was murdered
and found in a dumpster.
Holy shit.
Doesn't bring her back,
but at least I'm doing something positive about it.
-Insect Man.     -Yeah, um...
I've been bullied my whole life for being gay,
so now I stand up for the defenseless.
That's why I don't wear a mask.
Too much like being back in the closet.
Long as your heart's in the right place,
we don't care what you put in your mouth.
-Fist bump.     -Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Well, I became Battle Guy,
after my parents were mugged and killed coming home from the opera.
Did I tell you that sick bastard,
maxed out their credit cards on porno sites?
I hope we get the chance to say hello to this guy someday,
so I can personally levitate his soul from his body.
Oh, my God. Marty?
Yeah, I knew I recognized your voice.
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know no Marty. New guy.
Hey, asshole, it's me, Dave.
Dave? Why are you dressed like Kick-Ass?
Because I'm Kick-Ass.
You two know each other?
Yeah, like since we were five.
What's all this bullshit about your parents getting killed?
-Yeesh, language.     -What?
Battle Guy, care to update your resume?
Uh...
I'm trying to figure out how to explain this,
without sounding like a complete idiot right now.
Yeah, I'm not sure that's possible, Batman.
I'm not, either.
Um...
Okay. Well, when I found you guys online,
you were all swapping these awesome origin stories.
I mean, Colonel, you're ex-Mafia, for Christ's sake.
Yo. Don't take the Lord's name in vain.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you'd let me join the team,
unless I had a good story, too.
All right, we'll let you off the hook this time, Battle Guy.
-Wanna see something cool?     -Yeah.
I thought this could be our meeting room.
Whoa, this is so cool.
Now this little renovation was totally clandestine,
which means nobody knew about it.
Now, I know it's not much, but this is just the beginning.
Together we can make a real difference.
Whoa!
If you'd consider it, Kick-Ass,
we'd be honored to have you join us.
Hell, yeah!
That's what I like to hear.
Right, time for initiation.
Turn around and I'll unzip you.
I'm sorry, what?
Just joking. Let's get down to business.
Gotcha.
There you are.
We saved you a seat in the caf,
but you never showed.
I usually head over to the Olive Garden to carb load.
I haven't had white sugar since my first birthday.
Do we need a thintervention?
Come on, best way to tighten up a tummy is varsity dance team.
The sign-up sheet just went up.
It's still blowing my mind. Kick-Ass.
It's like finding out your best friend's,
always been Will Smith, you know?
Hi, guys. What are you talking about?
Nothing.
-Nothing?     -Yeah, Todd, nothing.
All right. See you around, guys.
Todd, wait.
-Ow, watch it.     -Watch me end your life.
Come on. Forget it.
Just one of the dickheads that follows The Motherfucker on Twitter.
Who?
The Motherfucker. He's some guy
claiming to be the world's first supervillain.
He's got 1,000 followers already.
What an asshole.
-Get some!     -Uh-huh! Yeah!
You got this, Motherfucker!
You really think he's got a shot?
I wouldn't take his money if I didn't.
MMA is like chess.
It's all about the moves.
And your boy really knows his stuff.
Time to die, asshole.
-You all right?     -I'm cool. Ow!
Good job. Nice jab, buddy.
Come on, stay loose, baby. Walk it off, walk it off.
-Oh!     -Shit!
Oh, you broke my leg!
-Come on. Do something.     -Let's take a break.
Yeah, yeah, let's take a break, guys. Come on.
Street rules, bitch!
Chuck! Get this girl off me!
Hey, what are you doing? What are you doing, man?
You all right, Chris? You all right, buddy?
Get off me! I was winning.
No, you were crying.
You know what? Screw this. My super power
is that I'm rich as shit.
Hey, you wanna work for me, huh?
You wanna beat people up for me?
-Sure.     -All right!
Let's get you a mask and a costume,
and we will call you Black Death.
Whoa, whoa, you don't think that's just a little bit incredibly racist?
I don't give a shit.
I want you to put the word out,
that I'm willing to pay top dollar, for every hired hitter in town.
Come on, come on. Just talk about it first.
Money talks.
You wanted me to be my own man.
This is what it looks like.
-All right, all right, I'll make some calls.     -Yes!
Anybody else wanna be a supervillain?
Promise I pay better than Chuck-little-dick-Liddell.
- What did you call me?  - No, no, man.
He took a hit to the head. Doesn't know what he's saying.
I've been studying privately with Coach Podell.
And by studying,
I mean my mom paid her off to make me varsity.
So, if you're half decent, I'll make sure she puts you on the team.
At least as an alternate.
You'd do that for me?
Besties stick together.
If Brooke wants a pet, she should just get a dog.
She's just trying to recreate Mindy in her own image.
All right, ladies, have a seat. Let's get started.
Mindy Macready?
Chill. As long as you don't fall on your face, you're in.
Go.
Four attackers.
No escape.
Oh, my God. You could totally make captain.
That was so much better than Brooke's.
Oh, my God.
Brooke doesn't stand a chance for captain after that.
A bunch of people with made-up names,
standing around in homemade costumes,
searching the web for unsolved crimes.
The comic book heroes all have billion-dollar bases
and headquarters on the moon, but this is the real world.
-Scales, like a red, white and blue.     -It's awesome.
- What's that?  - Brick.
Right.
-What do you think?     -I think it does the job.
People should get what they deserve.
Family living in the street deserves a hot meal.
An inebriated college girl deserves to make it home safe at night.
And a pervert, pedophile,
deserves a visit from Eisenhower.
Schwantz!
Ouch.
You don't wanna hit with your closed fist.
You might break your hand, then you're defenseless.
You wanna hit with open palm and pivot. Open palm and pivot.
Grab the back...
I never made varsity football,
or got cast in the school play.
Hell, I never even made honor roll.
Knock out, bitch!
But if I had,
I gotta believe it would've felt a lot like this.
When the cops can no longer protect and serve,
be warned, mugger, heads up, perv.
We got the strength, we got the nerve,
to give those in need what they deserve!
Justice Forever!
We were in the ultimate clique.
It didn't matter that no one else knew.
We knew. And we felt like rock stars.
-Good night, guys.     -Nice job. Battle Guy.
Night, Colonel. Thanks for everything.
No, son, thank you.
You showed us that every man can make a difference.
Without Kick-Ass, none of us would be here.
That's from the heart. Don't let it go to your head.
So...
I'm not really that tired.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm?
Mmm. Okay.
Let's leave the masks on.
-Yeah?     -Yeah.
Yeah!
First big mission's tonight,
and it's not community service.
We're taking on some real bad guys.
What, can't your team handle it?
They're not you, Mindy.
Remembering Tommy owns a dry fruit business.
Night Bitch teaches ballet.
Night Bitch? What is she?
A superhero or a soft core porno?
Maybe a little bit of both.
Oh, God, you're plugging her?
I'm gonna vom.
You're like a ninja.
Can't you just sneak out after Marcus goes to sleep?
You don't get it, Dave.
I made a promise to Marcus.
So break it. You're a superhero, remember?
Mindy Macready's just a disguise.
Yeah, well, I don't know what kind of superhero Night Whore is,
but if you really think I'd ever break my word,
you obviously have no idea who I am.
I know that making dance team doesn't make you stop being who you are.
I know Hit Girl couldn't give a shit,
about what high school girls are into.
I know that you wouldn't go on a date if your life depended on it.
Go to hell, Dave.
What? You know I'm right.
Hey! Roid Rage.
-Me?     -Yeah.
You wanna take me on a date sometime?
Uh, yeah. Sure. Um...
My name's, um, Simon.
Great, um, Simon.
It's a date.
Mindy, I'm sorry.
Is there a problem, Min?
Zero.
Good. Because I don't like problems.
Dave, you been sneaking out at night?
Mrs. Neipert said, she thought she saw you leaving at 2:00 in the morning.
Miss Neipert's crazy, Dad.
She tried to teach her dog Spanish.
Are you on drugs?
Seriously?
I gotta ask.
You're my best bud and you're growing up so fast.
Promise me you're not doing anything foolish?
Yeah, I promise.
Good enough for me, pal.
You're too smart to do anything stupid.
Justice Forever!
I'm glad you got that out of your system.
Oh, Todd texted me. Again. What a loser.
Dude, how bad-ass is Colonel Stars and Stripes?
Yeah, I still can't believe he's an ex-mob enforcer.
I mean, how do you go from that to being a superhero?
He's a born-again Christian.
-Shut up.     -Yeah.
Let's hope he can handle tonight.
I guess we're about to find out.
Hey. Where's the rest of the team?
Dr. Gravity has the flu,
and Remembering Tommy got Book of Mormon tickets, so...
That's okay.
Five of us should do.
How did you say this guy made his money, sir? Prostitution?
Not just girls. Kids. Ships them in from villages back home.
Boneheads in blue take a blind eye.
How do you know he's here tonight?
Because Thursday night is poker night.
Same five low-lifes every week.
Man with a habit ain't hard to find.
So what's the plan? Are we sneaking in?
I thought we'd knock. It's more polite.
What?
Stay frosty, team.
I used to eat punks like this for breakfast.
Jehovah's witness!
I'm sorry, I just zoned out for a second.
Did you say that we're going up against five gangsters?
And bouncer makes six.
And three-quarters.
What the fuck do you want?
Good evening, young man. We'd like a word with Jimmy Kim.
If it's not too inconvenient.
Get the fuck out of here before I tear your head off, you old fuck.
I'm sorry.
I think we're in trouble.
I just don't understand why people feel the need, to use that kind of language.
Whoa!
There he goes.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Battle Guy, what did I tell you about taking the Lord's name in vain?
Sorry, sir.
Eisenhower, at the ready.
Insect Man, I want you right behind me.
Everybody else spread out, catch the strays.
Oh.
And try to have fun,
otherwise what's the point?
Nice party. Anybody wanna dance?
Where are you going?
-Very nice.     -Behind you!
Watch the birdie.
Whoo!
Don't you move.
Night Bitch! Behind you!
Wait.
Look out!
Okay, I got his right arm.
You know, you shouldn't talk with your mouth full.
It's very rude. Come on.
Who the hell are you?
We're the good guys.
Oh, no, you're the fucking dead guys.
Eisenhower! Schwantz!
Oh!
Ow!
Where are the girls?
Come on, man. I've got a heart problem.
Oh, yeah?
No.
Do you want me to solve that for you?
Whoa, whoa!
Okay. The girls are upstairs in the apartments.
My little brother, he's on the till. He's just a college kid.
-Kick-Ass, Night Bitch.     -On it.
Ralph D'Amico is gonna end you for this.
Ow! It hurts!
Yeah, there's a dog on your balls.
You want money? There's 50 grand on the table.
Please just make him stop! Please!
You think you can buy us? Is that what you think?
We're not here to steal from you.
We're here to send a message to all the other bottom-dwellers.
-We're shutting you down.     -Come on.
There's a van waiting outside from a battered women's shelter.
It'll take you some place safe.
-Go. Go.     -We really can't leave.
We have no money.
Battle Guy, how much they have on the table?
Oh, it's like 50 grand.
You got plenty now.
Thank you.
Good job, guys.
Very tidy. Very tidy.
I can't believe you pulled a gun on that guy.
Were you really gonna shoot him?
Let you in on a little secret.
Empty. Don't tell the bad guys.
Pardon my language, Colonel, but you have got some serious balls.
Certainly more than Mr. Kim.
"There's a dog on my balls."
God damn it.
-Javier!     -What happened?
Some douche just posted a link to a story about a whorehouse,
says that Kick-Ass' team took them out.
What the hell? Where's my crew?
Chris, everybody's just...
Uh, can you ladies excuse us for a second?
Uh, no, they're my sidekicks. They can listen to what we have to say.
They're not your sidekicks, Chris.
They're prostitutes and witnesses, come on.
-All right.     -Sorry, no offense.
Everybody's just too afraid of your Uncle Ralph to take the job.
But he's in prison.
Doesn't matter. He runs the family now.
And he wants everybody to lay low.
But, fortunately for you,
Big Tony doesn't know how to lay low, so he's in.
-I don't remember a Big Tony. Is he huge?     -He's ironic.
5 foot 4, but mean as shit.
He's got such a hard-on for killing people.
-He's little and he kills.     -Right.
Call him "The Tumor."
Who's next?
All right, we've got, uh, an ex-Triad member looking for work.
Easy, "Genghis Carnage." Come on.
You gotta quit with the racist stereotypes, Chris.
Archetypes. Keep going.
We got, uh, Katarina Dumbrovski.
Wait, wait. A chick?
Yeah.
Seriously, you hired a chick?
Yeah. Former KGB.
She was locked up in the Gulag until she ate her cellmate.
Okay. "Mother Russia."
Mother Russia and Motherfucker both on the same team?
That doesn't work, Chris.
I am not asking for suggestions, asshole.
Just get them costumes and get them ready!
Shit.
Javier, thank you.
I couldn't do this without you.
You're pretty much like the only real family I have left.
Not a problem, man. I got your back.
It's kinda like you're the Alfred to my evil Bruce Wayne.
Did you just call me your fucking butler?
Yeah, is that not a compliment?
Shit. My bad.
There wasn't much action most nights.
I mean, there was always a little action with Night Bitch.
The reality of being a superhero is lots of patrols.
But that didn't stop people from begging to join up.
With all our new members,
it seemed kinda shitty not to ask Todd.
Stop peeking, man, you're gonna ruin it.
Check it out.
You can't fight crime in that.
Your pants are so tight, you got frog-eye.
What the hell's "frog-eye"?
-Male camel toe.     -What?
I'm not really sure about these names, either.
"Whup-Ass," "Kick-Ass-Man."
-"Dr. Kick-Ass"?     -Yeah.
Yeah, they all kinda seem derivative.
Let me translate that.
You can't just copy Dave's name, you knob-gobbler.
Okay. Um...
Uh...
Oh, wait. Oh, I got it.
I got it. I got it.
"Ass Kicker."
Seriously?
You're such a dick, Marty.
I know this is why you guys aren't texting me back,
I'm not an actual idiot.
Well, you could have fooled me, Ass-Licker.
-Yeah, well, screw you guys.     -Todd...
No, really. Fuck you guys.
I'm gonna go find my own team.
Todd. Wait. Come on.
Todd was right, we were being dicks.
But the truth is, the only person
I really wanted on the team was Mindy,
but she was too busy trying not to be a superhero.
Okay, Min, he's here.
Your first big date. How are you feeling?
Like the first time Big Daddy sent me into
a crack den with nothing but a penknife.
I've got some butterflies.
You just be yourself and you let me be nervous.
Don't worry about me. I can kill a man with his own finger.
A word of advice, I wouldn't open with that.
Thanks for letting me finally take you out.
Well, uh,
how else was I gonna get you to stop calling?
-Thanks.     -You're welcome.
Where are we going?
To a party.
Why is this party in the middle of nowhere?
Because that's where keg parties usually are, right?
Guess we're the first ones here.
This isn't where you have a party, moron.
This is where you dump a dead body.
What's your problem?
I'm sorry.
I'll stop being such a bitch.
You actually seem like a nice guy.
So, um...
you wanna hook up?
And a total idiot.
Simon, get back in the car.
Now!
Yay, you made it.
Brooke?
This is to celebrate you.
Celebrate?
What a total loser you are.
And we ditch losers.
Poor Mindy. What did you think?
The cool kids saw something special in you
and invited you to your first party
where you'd sip your first beer
and finally suck face for the first time?
Newsflash, you're not special.
Fuck with the queen bee and you're gonna get stung.
Date ditch.
Party at my house!
Pathetic.
Simon, you can drive us.
Dave?
Oh, my God! Mindy?
Holy shit. What are you doing?
Just needed to see my Robin, I guess.
Are you okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know what to do.
Those girls, they're...
they're evil.
It's just high school. Who gives a shit?
You should be out there in the real world making it a better place.
Dave, I can't.
I know, you promised your dad.
But he's not here anymore.
This is your life. You've gotta live it.
How am I supposed to face them tomorrow?
I'm so embarrassed.
Why?
You're smart. You're beautiful. You're funny.
You're the strongest person I've ever met. You can do anything.
And you're Hit Girl.
Doesn't matter if you're wearing a mask or makeup,
it's who you really are.
So what should I do? Cut their tongues out?
No! Definitely not.
I'm fucking with you.
Just beat them at their own game.
By being yourself.
Well, if you really wanna be popular,
consider two little words, "sex," "tape".
Lois, you don't need these ax wounds.
If I can dress like them, so can you.
It's a gift from some drug dealer who went missing.
Just because you dress like us,
doesn't mean you can be like one of us.
It doesn't matter what costume I wear, yours or mine,
I'm a superhero. That's who I am.
Okay, Captain Muffin-Muncher,
have fun playing make-believe.
This?
This is all make-believe, Brooke.
The reality is you're an evil bitch
who's just as bad as the worst criminal scum.
You wanna get real, Mindy?
In the real world, I win.
I go to an awesome college, I marry a hot guy
and I make adorable
babies for my nanny to take care of while we vacay in Paris.
My life is gonna rock and yours is gonna suck.
And no matter how slutty you dress,
no boy is ever gonna wanna kiss that hole you call a mouth.
So why don't you spare us all the whining and slit your wrists now?
'Cause the only thing that's gonna ruin my day
is looking at your face one more second.
-Told her.     -Damn.
What's that? A ghetto cell phone?
Gonna call for help with a come-back? Hmm.
Actually,
my daddy bought this from a disgruntled DARPA employee.
You see, it was designed for crowd control, but deemed too severe.
It emits a pulse that creates spontaneous nausea and diarrhea.
He called it "the sick stick."
Either your daddy got ripped off,
or you're back in make-believe land, sweetheart,
because we feel fabulous.
Not for long.
Oh, my God!
You get away from me. Please, you win.
I don't wanna win. I just want to make the world a better place.
Dad?
You home? Dad?
Is this what you've been up to while I'm out working nights saving for your college?
You've been dressing up and fighting people?
There is blood on these stick things.
What are you doing in my room?
I was looking for drugs.
I was worried about you.
Okay, good. Now you can stop.
No. Now I'm even more worried.
Jesus, Dave, drugs would have been better.
This is deranged.
Whoa. Some people do a lot worse.
Oh, the people you hang out with?
No. The people I hang out with are superheroes.
There is no such thing, Dave.
This is the real world with real consequences.
When are you gonna grow up?
If it means turning into you, never.
I don't wear the mask because I'm ashamed of who I am.
Not like you.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you're not at work, you're here doing crunches.
Why? So you can look like someone else?
Maybe get a few more years of doing nothing?
Your life has no meaning, Dad.
When you're gone, who's gonna notice?
Where the hell are you going?
Oh, uh, I'm leaving. That's what you do when you grow up.
Did he say why he wanted to see me?
When your Uncle Ralph calls, I don't ask questions.
Just the kid.
Chris, just be cool and you'll be fine.
Hey, how you doing?
Good, Uncle Ralph.
Listen, Chrissy, things have been tough all around since your dad,
you know.
Well, I been trying to get the family back on track from in here.
They record these things.
I know, it's fine.
The warden's a pal. Now listen to me.
It's okay to have a bit of fun,
but you can't go hiring a gang of heavy hitters.
Javier should have told you.
No, it doesn't matter.
Uncle Ralph, I am gonna make Kick-Ass pay for what he did to us.
Chrissy, you need to forget that punk.
It's more important that you stay out of this.
You're not like me, or your dad, you're, uh...
special.
You can't tell me what to do anymore.
I know who I am now.
Oh, yeah?
And who's that?
The Motherfucker.
You think you're the big bad guy, huh?
Let me show you what real evil looks like.
Hello?
Javier, what's going on?
Chris, what's up?
What are you doing on Lou's phone, huh?
Drop yours in the toilet again?
Everything okay?
Thank you for that. I needed it.
For what comes next.
Don't be stupid, Chris.
Just get out of town for a while. Go to college or something.
Why? You just taught me everything I needed to know.
Voila!
Presto and elegant, damn. Them boys designed a very tasty logo.
What's the matter, girl? You hear something?
Come on, let's go see. Come on!
Anybody out here?
I don't see anything.
Gonna have to stay in there until you calm down, you lunatic.
I wonder what's bothering you.
I know. Tonight you die.
Ladies first.
You will not shoot me.
You are superhero.
You help people. You do not hurt them.
That's supervillain territory.
Or as I like to call my little gang,
the Toxic Mega-Cunts.
Hi.
Yeah, like your head.
Yay!
Ooh, it's gotta hurt!
I did my homework on you, Colonel.
You used to be Sal Bertolini, didn't you?
Did a few jobs for my dad back in the day, before you got "born again."
I used to hang with a lot of losers.
Is this how you thought you'd die, Sal?
Dressed like an idiot?
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm The Motherfucker!
And I'm here to end Kick-Ass. Not just kill him.
I am gonna shit on everything that he loves.
Let's trash this place, guys.
"Miranda Swedlow"?
Who's that, Sal? She one of the whores on your team?
Night Bitch all snuggled up to Kick-Ass.
Looks like our boy's got a new hot pocket.
Want me to kill his dog?
The dog? Jesus Christ, I'm not that evil.
Cut the old man's head off.
You guys hungry? I'm starving. Come on.
Pizza, can we get pizza?
We're getting pizza.
Don't worry, I kill you first.
Justice For...
ever.
A Brooklyn resident was found decapitated last night.
According to Twitter, a man claiming to be
the world's first supervillain...
I told you, no TV. You're grounded, remember?
Marcus, I know I made you a promise,
but I can't keep being someone I'm not.
When I see evil, I have to stop it.
Mindy, what you did to those girls at school was unacceptable.
-You could have really hurt them.     -You're right, I could have,
but instead I sent them home with tummy-aches.
Boo-fucking-hoo.
I don't get it. This obsession that you have with revenge is not healthy.
If you don't let me and the police do our jobs,
there is gonna be nothing that I can do for you.
You're never gonna have a normal life
and you'll probably end up like your father.
Marcus, they cut a guy's head off.
Who else is going to stop them?
Kick-Ass? You?
You go to your room and do your homework.
Now!
Hey, guys, we're signing a sympathy card for the Colonel's sister.
You wanna go 5 bucks each so we can send flowers from the team?
Did you guys see The Motherfucker's Twitter page?
Who is this guy? And what's his problem with us?
I don't know, but he has got some elephant-sized balls.
He's been bragging on the web about what they did to the Colonel.
Can that be traced?
I tried. His IP address is masked.
All right, here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna organize a fight.
There are a lot of guys online who said they're in if we need them.
Are you kidding me? This isn't West Side Story.
We didn't join up to be in a gang.
We did this so we could help people.
Shannon's right. We need to leave this to the cops.
We better start walking in pairs.
Motherfucker's tweeted that the Colonel was just the beginning.
Anybody seen Night Bitch?
Are you sure she's on that team?
Stupid gash posted on her superhero page that
she's dating Kick-Ass.
So, yeah, I'm damn sure.
Hello, Night Bitch!
Hey.
Oh, she wants to take the party upstairs.
We're gonna have a party.
She closed the door.
Don't worry, darling, I'm not gonna kill you.
I want you to give a message to your boyfriend.
Come on, wriggly.
Let go!
You're done banging superheroes, baby.
It's time to see what evil dick feels like.
Shit.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Come on!
God, okay, I'm just... I'm not in the mood.
I guess evil dick feels limp.
Hurt her. Bad!
Cops are coming.
Leave it to Mother Russia.
She makes 10 times what we do.
Fifty thousand a week. Plus expenses.
Hey, watch out!
Wow!
Reverse it! Reverse it!
Don't move! Freeze!
Fifty thousand. She's worth it.
Whoa, whoa! Why are they backing up?
Why is there a lawnmower on the trunk?
Wow!
We need back-up, eight men down.
I think you mean 10.
Let's bounce!
Put the word out I'm building an evil army.
All psychopaths and ex-cons welcome.
I don't think you're gonna have a problem when people hear about this.
They just disappeared?
All they have to do is take off their masks,
no one's gonna recognize them once they're back in their street clothes.
Your attention, please!
Feds traced the IP addresses for all those other costumed freaks.
We got every law enforcement agency
in the state working to hit them at once!
Why is Kick-Ass on this list?
His crew does community service.
I don't give a shit. Anyone wearing a mask is getting detained.
We're putting an end to this tonight!
A lot of people said the cops were too heavy-handed that night.
But you gotta put it into context.
The police didn't mind our real life superhero stuff
as long as we were picking up litter
or helping old ladies cross the street.
But suddenly it was serious.
Suddenly we represented everything that was wrong with society.
Freeze!
Dad had warned me that the real world had real consequences.
As they pulled up, he must have been feeling pretty damn vindicated.
Oh, shit, Dave. What have you done?
Police, open up.
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, uh, it's me, Kick-Ass.
Wow.
You're actually pretty cute under that mask.
I'm so sorry about what happened.
Don't be.
It's my own fault.
We're gonna find these assholes and make this right.
What's the point?
I mean, we're really superheroes
about as much as we're really dating.
We don't even know each other's names.
I think it's time to get back to the real world.
I thought we were trying to make it a better place.
Then why is it worse?
Maybe Night Bitch was right,
which means Dad was, too.
I mean, things had gotten out of hand.
Maybe it was time for me to stop crashing at Marty's
and start apologizing.
Dad?
Whoa, whoa. That's my dad.
Your dad's Kick-Ass? What?
Yeah, he just gave himself up.
You don't understand. He's doing this to protect me.
Dad!
-Mindy?     -Dave?
I need your help. My dad's been arrested.
They think he's Kick-Ass.
Can you talk to Marcus?
-I'm grounded.     -So?
So that means I can't get involved.
-Look. Wait a second.     -I wish I could help.
Mindy! Are you on the phone?
Look, I gotta go, okay?
I'm sorry, Dave.
Mindy, wait, wait.
Hey, what the hell were you thinking?
Yeah, I could ask you the same thing.
I can't believe you lied to them.
I wasn't gonna do nothing while you went to jail.
I chose this. You should let me deal with the consequences.
I thought you wanted me to grow up.
Yeah? When you get a kid of your own one day, you'll understand.
I'm gonna tell them the truth.
No. Hey... It'll just make things worse.
Look, I spoke to my attorney.
He said they gotta let me out by tomorrow.
No actual crime was committed.
There are people out there who wanna kill Kick-Ass.
Well, the cops are out there looking for them,
so the safest place for Kick-Ass is right here, locked away.
I don't know how you got into all this shit, but
you gotta promise me you will never dress up in that outfit again.
Do you hear me?
I promise.
This evil lair owns!
Do people still say that, "own"?
Yeah, of course.
Your shark. Something's wrong.
Think you used the wrong kind of water.
What the hell, Eyal?
It's fine, Chris. They're supposed to lie at the bottom of the tank.
It's just their way of, how you say, settling into their environment.
Don't screw me on this, okay?
You said we'd be ready in two days,
we don't even have a men's room yet.
Don't worry.
What's with the bags of shit?
It's fertilizer for the bombs.
You're not a Supervillain if you don't have a plan to destroy the city.
It will not work. You need a chemical kind.
Do I have to do everything myself?
Just fix it!
You must relax. Everything is going as planned.
Mmm, no. No. Except it's not, okay?
That sad sack is not Kick-Ass.
I've seen Kick-Ass, he's like my age.
Guy's old enough to be his father.
No shit, right.
I'm sorry, who are you?
I... uh, volunteered for your evil army, like the others.
Right. I appreciate that. Thanks for joining the cause.
This is the VIP area for the core group.
I just thought it was funny you said that.
Because he is Kick-Ass' father.
Who?
Mr. Lizewski. He's Kick-Ass' dad.
Shut up!
Yeah. You're not gonna tell anyone, are you?
No.
But you, my friend, have just earned life-time access to my VIP area.
Go take a little seat.
Hey, get the kid a Frappuccino,
then put his little punk ass back to work.
Okay.
Come on.
Can I help you?
The Motherfucker wants us to take a picture with you.
It helps that my dad is a really good lawyer.
Because I don't think my beautiful ass
would last too long in prison.
Whoa, that's weird. Chris D'Amico just texted me a picture.
Red Mist? Whatever happened to that guy?
What is it?
Dude, what's wrong?
The next few days passed in a fog.
It didn't matter that I told the police about Chris,
they couldn't find him.
The cops did show up at Dad's funeral,
not out of respect,
but because they were scared something would happen.
My dad was a decent man.
All he ever did was try and give me a good life,
and I told him no one would notice when he was gone.
I love you, pal.
I love you, too, Dad.
You guys came.
We'd love to help you track down this Chris D'Amico d-bag, but
we just got out on parole.
No, that's fine.
I'm not looking for revenge.
Last thing I promised my dad was that I was gonna give this up.
That's exactly what I'm gonna do.
But you started this.
Now I'm ending it.
Dave, I'm so sorry. Do you hate me for not helping?
No, not even a little bit.
You were right. You gave it up.
If I had, too, my dad would still be alive.
The only person I blame is myself.
Let's do this!
Get down!
Mindy!
Spread out!
Keep your head down!
Come on!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Get him!
Get that van over here!
Hurry up!
Mindy?
Mindy!
You gotta put this on.
I'm not gonna do it.
There's nothing left you can do to hurt me.
You wanna bet?
Whoa! Whoa!
Game on, cocksuckers!
There's a girl on the roof!
She's still up there!
-I think I got her!     -Go check!
Get out there!
Come on! Move your head.
Pull over, pube-face.
We know Chris D'Amico is The Motherfucker.
Where is he hiding?
Eat a dick.
You're gonna eat yours if you don't start talking.
Go ahead and shoot me, you little bitch.
There's nothing you can do that would make me talk.
Look, hold on. I can't do this right now. It's my dad's funeral.
Dave, your father loved you.
Just like my daddy loved me. And I know it hurts, but maybe,
maybe that's the real meaning of being a superhero.
Is taking that pain and turning it into something good.
Something right.
Remember what you told me?
This is your life. You've gotta live it.
Now help me find some pliers. I'm gonna make this guy eat his own dick.
Seriously?
-Hello?     -Marcus?
Mindy. What's going on? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
We know where The Motherfucker's hiding.
He's recruiting an army of supervillains and making homemade bombs.
Marcus, he wants to burn the city down.
You promised me.
I know you see me as this little girl,
but I'm not and I never was.
You're right.
Daddy did take my childhood away,
but I'm not so sure that was a bad thing.
Marcus, he gave me a gift,
a gift that I can't escape no matter how hard I try.
And I don't need to spend the next four years of my life
trying to figure out who I am
because I already know.
I'm Hit Girl.
I posted the address. Do you think they'll show?
Chris has an army.
These real life super dweebs have been waiting their whole lives for a call like this.
Are you okay?
What? Yeah, no... I'm fine.
Here.
Take this.
"Last resort" really isn't my style.
Dave, this isn't a comic book.
Real people are going to die tonight.
My daddy was prepared for anything.
Are you?
Yeah.
I am.
They should be back by now!
It's definitely dead.
Says on the Internet you're supposed to keep them in fresh water.
It is just hungry. We must feed it.
Why are you looking at me?
We gotta get this shit started.
Oh, yeah. Have I got a show for you bitches!
Motherfucker, Motherfucker...
All right, party people!
We are gonna kill Kick-Ass,
the very first superhero, together.
We are gonna cut him up into little pieces,
feed that shit to MC Shark
and post it all over YouTube. For real!
He's kidding, right?
Motherfucker don't kid.
That's not it. I'm gonna give each and every one of you
party favor fertilizer bombs!
And we are gonna get our riot on!
That's what it means to be evil.
We, my friends, are the real 1%,
and tonight we are gonna fuck this city up or my name is not...
Chris D'Amico!
That is not my name!
No, you're right. Your new name's Little Bitch.
Oh, this is perfect.
Are you really that stupid?
There's two of you and a whole army of us.
Do you really have such a hard-on to die?
No.
That's why we brought our friends.
What's the matter, Chris? Shit hit your shorts?
Yeah, and I'm gonna wipe my ass with your face.
You're gonna pay for what you did to my dad.
Your dad? You blew up my dad with a bazooka.
Oh!
Are you ready to die, little girl?
I might be if I have to keep looking at that shit-stain you call a face.
Chris!
Hold him down. I wanna see what his guts look like.
That's enough from you boys!
Nicely done, sweetheart.
That all you got?
No, I got my lethal zero G device.
Bullshit.
No shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thanks. Ass Kicker.
Nice.
Jesus, you are such a pussy.
What is the point of wearing a mask if you can't do what you want?
We want to do good.
No, people want to win the lottery.
People want to fuck Scarlett Johansson.
You think you can kill me with little needle?
That's not what it's for.
It's called adrenaline, bitch.
What was that, some cheap shot?
That was for the Colonel.
Ahh!
That's for Night Bitch.
And that's for my dad.
What the hell are you doing?
Saving your whiny ass!
No!
I won't let you have this. I'd rather die!
What is wrong with you, dude? This is not a comic book, it's real life!
When you're dead, it's done. There's no sequel.
You made this real. You started it!
And I'm gonna finish it.
I'll be immortal, like an evil Jesus.
Wait!
I'm alive.
Dave, I'm so sorry.
The feeling was indescribable.
Chris D'Amico, dead.
His wannabe supervillains, defeated.
But did we make the world a better place?
Or did we just finish something
that began when I first put on this mask?
The cops are coming.
They'll take care of the bad guys.
We better skedaddle before they get here.
We did it.
Fuck, yeah.
Hey, language.
You're right, if we're gonna dress like heroes, we should act like heroes.
He'd be proud of you, Dave.
He'd be proud of all of us.
You know we can never do this again, right?
It's over.
One last time. Come on.
What do you say, Hit Girl? Are you in?
Why the hell not?
Justice Forever!
Thanks for the ride.
I'll see you at school.
I'm leaving New York, Dave.
I can't go home. I can't put Marcus in that position.
Why? He won't arrest you.
You just saved the city.
Yeah, well, I also killed six guys with a cop's gun.
Vigilantes don't get a free pass.
You can't go. People need you.
-They've got you now.     -Mindy...
I'm not like you.
You don't have to be a bad-ass to be a superhero, Dave.
You just have to be brave.
What was that?
That was my first kiss.
Be nice
or I'll rip your ass out through your mouth.
When Mindy left,
that's when I finally understood where my life was going.
Just like it had to eventually happen,
that real people would try to be superheroes.
Eventually it had to end, too.
Superheroes can't exist in the real world
for a reason.
It's because the real world needs real heroes.
And not some punk in a wet-suit playing dress-up,
but a genuine bad-ass who can really kick ass.
Hello?
Please. Don't go.
Don't go.
Is anybody there?
Hello?
Some help, please?
A shark bit my fucking dick off and I can't get some water?
特攻聯盟２
稍早前…
同一時間…
城市的另一邊…
約在包利街墨菲酒吧後門
你爸爸會希望你來的
因為我爸，所以我才不能參加什麼團體
你不懂的，掰
罰錢罐
當夜稍晚…
跟你10元
老大，外面有人
我花錢不是請你來打手槍的
到你了
有沒有搞錯啊…
紐約市立看守所
所有超級英雄請注意，我們需要你
還以為你這個王八蛋多耐操
別走 後面還有
手槍子彈時速超過700哩
絕對不可能，你想太多了，不行
沒問題，我不喜歡勉強別人
很好，別射我
沒差
靠！我還活著
哦!
太神奇了！
對吧，所以…
嗯
再來一次？
死都不要
沒差
說『沒差』卻開槍射我胸口
麥擱鬧啊
我超不爽
算了，小孬孬
我一直納悶之前怎麼沒有超級英雄
其實是有的，那就是明蒂麥奎迪
她爸死後…
以前的同事馬庫斯成了監護人
-她拿粉紅色小馬背包？  -真可愛
謝謝
從幼稚園偷來的？
馬庫斯每天送她上學
他前腳一走，她後腳開溜
老師沒發現
因為她駭進學校伺服器
還頒給自己全勤獎
超殺女和大老霸才真是狠角色
明蒂的宿命
就是終結罪惡
但無論撂倒多少毒梟
她依然難掩孤單
至於我?我不太想當超級英雄
因為實在太危險了
但問題是…我會無聊死
我就像一般高中生
不清楚人生方向
干，連想看哪一台都不知道
只是看個電視，又不是在說中東問題
我的麻吉陶德和馬堤完全不知道…
我就是那紅透半邊天的元祖超級英雄
昨晚有看蜘蛛人嗎？
我看到梅姨竟然會硬奇怪吧？
有戀祖情結的就不怪了
不是萬聖節他們也變裝
他們是正港的超級英雄…
自從第一位市民穿起超人裝
這兩年來…
大家已經開始爭相效仿
我是因為屌爆俠所以才變身超級英雄
下班回家不久…
就整裝待發，外出巡邏
幫大家維護社區安全
我激勵了大家走上街頭
自己卻宅在家裏
所以那天晚上吃飽
我就把超人裝拿了出來
-抱歉  -哇!你不會敲門嗎？
你要知道撫摸自己是很正常的
天呀，爸，給我出去！
如果我真的要考慮屌爆俠的復出
我就應該認真一點
可以聊聊嗎？
明蒂拜託？
快上車，還在跳表
我想像蝙蝠俠、羅賓一樣組個團隊
沒人想演羅賓
羅賓哪裏不好？
你不就像大老霸身邊的羅賓？
羅賓還恨不得是我咧
我想說的是，我們應該成為夥伴
你和我，就像二重奏一樣
我都進了大聯盟，你還在打少棒
所以呢？你可以訓練我
我想當真正的英雄
而你幾乎已經算是超級英雄了
單打獨鬥不累嗎？
你難道不想找些夥伴？
可以能幫你分擔的人？
我說什麼你都照做？
當然
揍我
你才15歲…
搞屁呀？
小孬孬只有挨打的份
哇靠
明蒂像男生的『朝旗』…
連續三周照三餐打我
防守！左、右，防守！
就算我末梢神經受損
依然生不如死
不過很怪，我挺爽的
總算找到努力的目標
-你的臉怎麼了？  -沒什麼
彷彿朝著什麼目標邁進
哇靠！
你太猛了！
其他人都在假扮超級英雄
但我們是要成為真正的英雄
我必須瞞著女友凱蒂、馬堤與陶德
但我不再意，因為這太好玩了
左、右、左！
我們是超級英雄聯盟
啥咪嚨無驚
搞什麼，媽？你刪掉我錄的新聞？
對，我做的，克裏斯多夫
那是屌爆俠的新聞
克裏斯多夫，別再追那個超級英雄了
他不是超級英雄，他是殺人兇手
他用火箭炮殺了爸爸，你醒醒
爸是火燒死的
火？你有問題嗎？
你！你才是我的問題！
我一直希望你能成為一個正常的小孩
所以我才在你爸的意外後，搬到長島
火箭筒才不是意外
你這個智障老太婆！
別說了
很好，我要走了
拜託！哈維爾，上道一點
抱歉，可是你媽請我不是因為我上道
我恨你！在家自修就像坐牢一樣
你還丟掉赤霧俠的服裝
媽的，我沒有病，你才有！
我-要-你-嗝-屁！
媽？
別碰
抱歉，那是什麼？
最後的武器…在你快死的時候用
你不怕…死嗎？
你不怕你再也長不高了嗎？
我是說真的
就算是蜘蛛人或蝙蝠俠也會死
如果你怕死，只有一件事是確定的
你死定了
我爸從來不怕死
他的下場不也是…
他知道總有一天要做出最終的犧牲
所以要我發誓
繼續捍衛這座城市
如有違背
不得好死
你爸是瘋子，你知道吧？
你錯了，戴夫
我爸才是第一個正港超級英雄
你和赤霧俠都不是，我爸才是
為他做事真的很光榮
明蒂，今天上學好玩嗎？
超瘋的
今天穆林老師休假，庫柏先生代課
無聊到爆
怪了，因為校長昨天打電話來說
你要領全勤獎
卻從沒有來上課
我跟蹤你，卻發現你和一個男生上車
後來在橋上跟丟了
可以告訴我去了哪裏嗎？
對不起，我不是故意惹你生氣
別假哭了，你15歲了，不是5歲
我說了
他要我蹺課，一起去逛購物中心
所以我就去了
這和超殺女無關吧？
我不會在床底下發現飛刀和飛鏢吧？
不會的，我只是希望他喜歡我
蹺課不是求愛的好方法
-我真笨  -嘿，嘿
你是最聰明的小女孩，去吃披薩吧
我不用被禁足嗎？
這次先記警告
真的想丟光你媽的遺物？
不然要怎麼處理她的鬼東西？
哇靠，她有一對…
老兄，她死了，別再肖想她的奶子
我是說這個
天哪，那是我爸的
何不自己留著？
可以嗎？
當然，這是你的了
聽著，克裏斯…你現在是當家的
-小心一點就好，知道嗎？  -災啦
哇!
你絕對不想要這個！
我來處理
你今天先回家吧，再見
嘿
準備好第一波實戰演練了沒？
這些要幹嘛？
穿上…然後去釣魚
沒有皮條客像我這麼白
聽好了，下一條街右轉
從弗萊布許大道出來
不扮屌爆俠沒關係嗎？
這才是重點
屌爆俠不是一套服裝，而是真實的你
戴夫萊佐斯基才是你的面具
看來我的『面具』要被打慘了
死Gay炮，這些袋子幹嘛的？
說你要拿12寸的按摩棒捅他老母
我只是在散步
這不是我的作風，我都直接找警察
你在跟誰說話？
我只是在講電話
這裏的收訊…爛透了
袋子給我，死娘炮
別逼我讓你吸大屌
快點
好啦，好啦
這幾周來我讓明蒂扁到痛哭流涕
就是為了再來這裏挨打
搞什麼鬼
想死嗎？死娘炮！
你們一直講那些屁話，看起來更娘
手下留情…
再讓我發現你搶劫…你這個屎漢堡
我就會扯爆你菊花再砍斷你的髒手
答應我再也不做壞事了
我答應你
鬼才信
-怎麼樣？  -你差點害死我
不是啦，我是說我的台詞
『鬼才信』我想了一大堆
快走！我會說你救了我，走吧！
女性嫌犯逃離弗萊布許大道
不到5尺，蒙面，手持雙節棍和劍
-明蒂  -馬庫斯，怎麼了？
你接了電話
表示你不在學校
我…
我不舒服，所以護士決定叫我回家
真可憐，我快到家了
等下煮個湯，一起看『百萬小學堂』
好啊，待會見羅
待會見
糟了!
我的湯呢？
讓我看你有沒有發燒
流真多汗
睡一下就會好了
先休息一下，我去煮湯
那是血嗎？
為什麼騙我，我不會再放任你了
我和你爸情同兄弟
他是好警察也是英雄
但大老霸呢？他不是你爸
他剝奪了你的童年
還有這個…
超殺女？也不是真正的你
你是明蒂麥奎迪，剛上高中
你現在還不認識真正的自己
但你會的，只要去嘗試
我不想
你不知道自己想要什麼
你還小，還太早
我15年來的經歷，已經勝過很多大人
你爸留下的紙條
就是他死後我們才看的那張
寫了什麼？
你會照顧我
你應該聽我的話，對吧？
你聽好
我希望你上學，別再跟那個男生來往
你還要答應我
別再發生這種事
如有違背
不得好死
很好
明蒂！
怎麼了？
你先害我差點沒命，然後搞失蹤
戴夫，對不起
我…真的？
沒錯
我真的很對不起
好吧，隨便你
我是說…你不像是會道歉的人
你要我講幾遍？
我們走吧
今天別太大力，我好像肋骨斷了
我不幹了
今天不想訓練？
什麼都不幹了
等一下，你是說…全部？
不行，你可是超殺女
不是才要組團，你怎麼能一走了之
放棄你的宿命
再也不是了，戴夫
對不起，可是結束了，我不幹了
剛才她是在跟他分手?
別理我了
不要再跟我道歉了
到底是哪個比較噁心，是跟國中生上床
-還是被國中生甩了？  -哇，哇!
戀童癖
不是這樣的
不然呢？請告訴我
我不能說，這和屌爆俠有關
我也有事情瞞著你，記得馬利克嗎？
針具交換站的志工？
他的『棒子』比屌爆俠…大上好幾倍
-騙人  -是真的
我說的『棒子』是屌
我懂，謝了
睡過15歲是要坐20年牢的，變態
跟國三的搞？有夠壞的
有問題嘛？毛都長了當然可以玩
當然不是
克裏斯，家教來了
克裏斯！
克裏斯，你…
靠北，你幹嘛穿成這樣？
我的宿命
只因為你老母最近有點起肖？
我有我的宿命
我爸曾是黑道老大，這就說得通了
我會進化成超級壞蛋
快點
克裏斯，把槍放下，免得傷到別人
我不是克裏斯
好吧，赤霧俠…
赤霧俠是我以前當超級英雄的名字
從今以後，叫我…
臭B王
自從明蒂退出江湖…
我決定不再練拳，直接上街巡邏
屌爆俠，歡迎回來！
-耶!  -哇!
你是最屌的！
唯一的問題是，我依然孤軍奮戰
所以我上網找到一個物理教授
他自稱『重力博士』
他當然比不上超殺女，但聊勝於無
我發明的零重力裝置
可以抬起一噸重的東西
真的假的？
這麼好騙，這只是球棒包著錫箔紙
你還是上當了
我要一罐健怡汽水
我甚至不是物理系教授
我只是在廣告公司寫文案的
這就是我喜歡的原因
我可以成為任何人
你經常打團體戰？
算吧，不…其實沒有
有人陪可以壯膽
我也這麼想，我從來沒有打過架
我也希望你不會碰到
我有個臉書朋友想組團
我不確定他有多認真
但他照片挺酷的
真的嗎？這就是我聯絡你的原因
我不敢太早提出來，怕嚇到你
我小個便就開他的檔案給你看
你叔叔拉夫看到會生氣的，克裏斯
別叫我克裏斯
我不會說你的新名字
你的老大起初是我爸
再來是我媽，現在換我
我大概是全紐約最有錢的小孩
看不慣就回家吃自己吧！
屌爆俠！
老兄，很高興見到你
需要我幫忙嗎？
幫我把影片點閱率衝破一百萬
來吧，來吧
快跑，屌爆俠，快跑！
去你媽的紐澤西爛咖！
一對一就不行了嗎？
那不算一對一，明天有聚會
地址再傳給你
當心重力博士！
你忍不住佩服博士的熱血
我超期待見到他的朋友
手舉高，春卷先生
現金拿出來，別干蠢事
快點！攝影機在哪裏？
-太貴了，這裏沒有  -不會吧？
恁娘咧！這樣怎麼出名？
你想被拍？
閉嘴，趴在地上！
你最好告訴大家『臭B王』來過
你頭殼壞掉嗎，孩子？
你也趴著，甘道夫
不然就炸了你的屁眼
槍拿好，不然後座力會轟了你的臉
快趴在地上！
媽的，給我快一點！
我就說吧
走！快走！
發動車子！快走！
太爽了！
我覺得整個人都活起來了
我終於看清了我的宿命
我要摧毀全世界
讓大家都知道臭B王！
找一些頂尖的綜合格鬥選手來訓練我
譬如喬克李戴爾
我不在乎要花多少錢
我只想親手殺了屌爆俠
這個值得推特一下
好羅，可以了嗎？
不知道耶，我行嗎？
你行的，你很漂亮
布魯克人也很好
我要跟她們聊些什麼？
我寧願被刑求，也不要看小賈斯汀
-你會玩得很開心  -我會搞砸的
你又知道了？
因為那是他媽的睡衣派對
說髒話要罰錢
換大一點的吧
酷吧？這是用來運送啤酒的
老兄，你的地下總部竟然有秘密電梯
我跟你提過這間屋子的主人
這分明就是蝙蝠洞
-完全同意  -贊啦
這是我一生中看過最酷的時刻
歡迎加入正義永存聯盟
威廉斯探員，這想必是明蒂
你猜對了
你們玩得開心點，早上再來接你
我會割腕自殺
不，你的指甲會修得漂漂亮亮
-是嗎？  -相信我
女孩們，跟明蒂打招呼
嘿
我認識你
你就是騎過戴夫搖桿的國中生
我沒有騎…
如果只是吹，那還能算處女
看她就知道她沒吹過
那舔屁眼？打手槍？戳菊花？
天啊，至少有親他吧？
當然
你從沒親過男生吧？
天呀！好可愛喔
說不定她是T婆
說不定我會踹你個雞巴
她有夠嗆，我喜歡
有什麼大不了
不過是喇舌而已
喇舌當然很爽
就像看Union J的MV時的感覺
不會吧，你不知道他們？
這個會改變你的世界
♬ 別說你很孤單，我來幫你分憂解勞 ♬
♬ 我會一直守候著你 ♬
你們比史丹李的男粉絲還瘋吧？
誰是史丹李？
♬ 我會抱著你，我會抱著你 ♬
♬ 我會抱著你 ♬
♬ 你知道我會抱著你 ♬
♬ 你彷彿跑了幾個小時 ♬
♬ 上氣不接下氣 ♬
♬ 惡魔在你腦中大聲尖叫 ♬
♬ 你疲累了，你受傷了 ♬
♬ 你備受艱辛，你傷痕纍纍 ♬
♬ 但別想太多，只要撐住 ♬
♬ 我會抱著你 ♬
什麼鬼東西？
對吧，我都濕了
這就是你
我們的穿著和談吐也許不太一樣
但說到男生，我們都哈到不行
暮光之城、查寧坦圖、Union J
這是生物本能，小蕩婦，別抗拒它
我…
我要走了
但我們要去羅根小屋哈草狂歡
我想給你班上女生搶破頭的機會
你難道不想每天穿著緊身衣出門…
接受大家的膜拜？
你難道不想夜晚偷溜出去…大鬧一場
讓全世界知道
你是多麼堅強獨立？
你難道不渴望歸屬感？
♬ 你知道我會抱著你 ♬
我能穿這樣去嗎？
當然!
一定會很好玩
我們找過警察…也找過記者
甚至架過…那個什麼…對，網站
請大家幫我們尋找湯米
呃…
但都沒用，我們再也沒有見到兒子
我就發起一個『別忘了湯米』的活動
每週三次
星條旗上校從網路找到我們
你們太慘了，真的很遺憾
自從我妹遭到謀殺，棄屍垃圾桶後
我就化身暗夜騷貨
天啊
雖然無法挽回她
至少對社會有幫助
-蟲人換你  -是…
我是同性戀，一直受到霸凌…
現在我挺身為弱勢發聲
所以我不戴面具
不想再羞於見人
只要心存正義
誰管你嘴巴含什麼
-擊拳吧  -謝謝上校
我爸媽看完歌劇
回家遇襲身亡，我就變身單挑王
我有告訴過你們嗎？
那傢伙還在色情網站刷爆他們信用卡
希望我們會遇上他
我會親自揍到他魂飛魄散
不會吧，馬堤？
我認得你的聲音
不，我聽不懂你在說什麼
我不認識馬堤，新來的
混帳，是我，戴夫
戴夫？你幹嘛扮成屌爆俠？
因為…我就是屌爆俠
你們認識？
對，五歲就認識了
你幹嘛瞎掰父母遭到謀殺？
-別說髒話  -什麼？
單挑王，不介意更新履歷表吧？
呃…
我一直煩惱該怎麼自我介紹…
才不會像個白癡
這大概很難，蝙蝠俠
我也這麼想
呃…
當我遇見你們…
你們都超有故事的
星條旗上校，混過黑道，超神的
別妄稱神的名
對不起
我想沒有好故事
你就不會讓我加入
這次放過你，單挑王
-想看酷的東西嗎？  -想
這可以當成會議室
太酷了
我偷偷的完成改裝
所以沒人知道
目前還很陽春，但只是開始
我們可以一起改變世界
喔!
屌爆俠，如果你願意加入我們
我們深感榮幸
當然啦！
我就是想聽到這個
好啦，開炮了
背對我，褲子我來脫
什麼？
玩笑話，幹正事了
被耍了吧
找到你了
我們幫你留了位置
你都沒來
我通常會去餐廳補充碳水化合物
我一歲以後就沒吃過糖
你怕胖嗎？
收小腹的秘訣就是參加舞蹈校隊
報名表就在公佈欄上
我還是不敢相信你就是屌爆俠
這就像好朋友的…
真實身份是威爾史密斯
你們好，聊些什麼？
沒什麼
-沒什麼？  -對啊，陶德，隨便聊
好吧，待會見
陶德，等一下
-小心  -小心我斃了你
算了
大概是臭B王的粉絲吧
誰?
臭B王？
他自稱是全世界第一個超級壞蛋
目前有一千個粉絲
真是腦殘
-來啊!  -哈!來吧!
臭B王，你沒問題的！
他真的有可能贏嗎？
不然就退錢
綜合格鬥就像下棋
戰術才是關鍵
那小子沒問題的
死期到了，俗辣
-沒事吧？  -我很好
打得好，這拳真猛，老兄
放輕鬆，孩子，撐下去
-哦!  -可惡！
你打斷我的腿！
-快想辦法  -中場休息
是啊，暫停一下，夥計們，來吧
這麼不小心啊，死娘泡！
恰克！把他拖走！
你太超過了
沒事吧，老弟？
閃開，我要贏了
不，你哭了
你懂什麼？算了，我的力量就是…
…他媽的有錢
想為我工作嗎？
想幫我K人嗎？
-想  -很好！
我們會提供面具和服裝
你就叫…黑死病
你不覺得有點種族歧視嗎？
那又怎樣？
放話出去…
我重金募集鎮上職業殺手
我們先談一談
有錢好辦事
你希望我獨立
我不就照做了？
-我再打電話問問  -好極了！
還有誰想成為超級壞蛋？
我保證比小屌哥喬克李戴爾付得多
你叫我什麼？
他打到腦震盪，不知道自己在說什麼
教練波德爾是我的私人家教
其實家教只是幌子
我媽賄賂她，讓我加入校隊
只要表現不要太差，我保證你可以
至少可以當候補隊員
你會幫我？
姐妹淘分什麼彼此
如果布魯克想養寵物，她應該買隻狗
明蒂只是她的最新嗜好
各位同學，找位置坐，要開始了
明蒂麥奎迪？
別緊張，只要不摔倒，你就過關了
去吧
四個壞蛋
無路可逃
你簡直可以當隊長了
布魯克差遠了
天啊
布魯克沒機會當隊長了
一群人取了假名…
穿著自制服裝
上網搜尋懸案
漫畫英雄都有造價幾十億的基地
以及月球總部，但這是真實世界
-…分階段，紅白藍  -真酷
-那是什麼？  -磚塊
然後呢
-怎麼樣？  -挺不錯的
人民應該過著更好的生活
遊民應該吃到熱呼呼的食物
酒醉女大生應該安全返家
至於變態和戀童癖…
就應該見一見艾森豪
『德語』
雞雞！
好痛
你不會想用拳頭的
因為骨頭可能會斷掉，你就無法防守
你要用迎面掌…換邊…迎面掌…換邊
抓住頸後…
我沒參加過足球校隊…
也沒演過校內話劇
我連資優生也沒當過
死了吧，賤貨!
如果我曾經風光過…
大概就是這種感覺吧
當警察再也無法提供保護時…
搶劫犯和性變態你們給我聽好
我們有力量，我們有膽量
幫助需要的人，給他們應得的一切！
正義永存！
我們是一個終極團隊
大家不認識我們沒關係
我們知道就夠了，我們就像超級巨星
-晚安，夥計們  -幹得漂亮，單挑王
晚安，上校，感謝你所做的一切
沒什麼，孩子，謝謝你
你讓大家明白，人人都可以改變世界
沒有屌爆俠，就沒有我們
這都是真心話，但別自我膨脹
現在呢？
我還不會很累
嗯
嗯?
好吧
別摘下面具
-真的？  -真的
好吧!
今晚有大任務…
而且不是社區服務
我們要對付幾個惡煞
怎麼？你們不行嗎？
他們不是你，明蒂
湯米賣乾燥水果
暗夜騷貨教芭蕾舞
暗夜騷貨？她是誰？
是超級英雄還是AV女優？
都是吧
天哪，你上過她？
我要吐了
你就像女忍者一樣
難道不能趁馬庫斯睡覺偷溜出來？
你不懂的，戴夫
我答應過馬庫斯
那就反悔啊，你忘了你是超級英雄？
明蒂麥奎迪只是個幌子
我不懂暗夜騷貨是哪門子的超級英雄
但如果你覺得我會反悔…
那表示你不夠瞭解我
加入舞蹈校隊並不妨礙你追求自我
超殺女根本不屑
女高中生的玩意
你才不是超想約會的那種女生
去死吧
幹嘛？被我說中了
壯壯小帥哥
-叫我嗎？  -對啊
想約我出去嗎？
想啊…
我叫…賽門
好，賽門
約好嘍
明蒂，很抱歉
有問題嗎，明蒂？
沒事
很好，我不喜歡看到問題
戴夫，你晚上都偷溜出去？
奈波太太看到你凌晨兩點出門
奈波小姐瘋了，爸
她教小狗西班牙文耶
你有嗑藥嗎？
真的這樣想？
我一定要問
你是我最好的哥們，你也長大了
答應我別做傻事？
好，我答應你
這樣就夠了，哥們
你很聰明，不會做傻事的
正義永存！
你能這樣紓解壓力不錯
陶德又傳訊息了，死阿宅
星條旗上校到底有多可怕啊？
真不敢相信他以前是混黑道的
黑道哪有可能變成超級英雄？
他是重獲新生的基督徒
-少來了  -是真的
祈禱他今晚能全身而退
我們很快就會知道了
其他人呢？
重力博士感冒了
湯米弄到音樂劇的票…
沒關係
我們5個就夠了
這個人靠什麼維生？脅迫賣淫？
不只女人也有小孩的，都偷渡過來的
白癡警察坐視不管
你怎麼知道今晚他在？
因為星期四是撲克之夜
五個人渣準時出現
有習性的人並不難找
計劃是什麼？偷偷進去？
我想敲個門，這樣比較有禮貌
什麼?
大家保持冷靜
對我來說這算小事一樁
耶和華的見證人！
對不起，我剛沒聽清楚
你是說對付5個黑道嗎？
外加一個保鏢，總共6個
又四分之三
啥咪代志？
晚安，少年仔，我們想找大金聊聊
如果他方便的話
給我滾，不然就折斷你的頭，死老頭
打擾了
有麻煩了
搞不懂為何大家都愛耍狠
喔!
搞定一個了
神呀
單挑王，我怎麼說的？別亂說妄語
我錯了，上校
艾森豪，準備好
蟲人，跟在我後面
其他人散開，別讓人溜了
哦
試著找樂子…不然…
有什麼意義呢？
這麼熱鬧，有人想跳舞嗎？
往哪跑？
-做的好  -小心後面！
注意了
哇!
別動
暗夜騷貨！你後面！
留情
小心！
好，我來銬他右手
滿口食物不要說話
沒禮貌
你算哪根蔥？
我們是正義的使者
不，你們死定了
艾森豪！雞雞！
夠勁!
嗷!
女孩呢？
放過我吧，我有心臟病
是喔？
不要…
要我幫你嗎？
哇咧，哇咧!
我招了，女孩都在公寓樓上
我弟負責收錢，他還在念大學
-屌爆俠、暗夜騷貨  -包在我身上
拉夫達米柯會斃了你！
痛！
是啊，德國狼犬就愛廣東咸蛋
錢都給你，桌上有五萬塊
拜託誰來阻止它！拜託！
你以為可以收買我們？真的這麼想？
我們不是來搶錢的
我們是來打廣告的…告訴其他死雜碎
-這裏勒令停業  -過來…
外面有受暴婦女庇護所專車
你們會到一個安全的地方
-上車吧  -我們走不了
我們沒有錢
單挑王，桌上有多少錢？
大概有五萬塊
夠多了吧
謝謝
大伙幹得好
好極了，好極了
沒想到你會拿槍指著他
真的會射他嗎？
說一個小秘密
空的，別告訴那些壞蛋
我就直說了，上校，你超有種的
肯定比大金多
『那狗在咬我蛋蛋』
可惡！
-哈維爾  -怎麼了？
有個蠢蛋貼了制服店的消息
屌爆俠那群人把那裏掀了
搞什麼？我的人呢？
大家都…
小姐，你們可以離開一下嗎？
不，她們是我的助手，不用擔心
她們不是你的助手
她們是妓女兼證人
-好吧  -抱歉，無意冒犯
大家都怕你叔叔拉夫所以沒人做大
但他還在坐牢
沒差，現在整個家族都歸他管
他希望大家維持低調
但算你好運
大湯尼不懂得避風頭，所以他加入了
-沒印象，他很大只嗎？  -小矮子
五尺四寸而已，但狠到不行
他以殺人為快樂之本
-矮冬瓜卻很能殺  -沒錯
叫他『致命腫瘤』吧
下一個？
他混過中國黑道
簡單『成吉癡漢』下一個
你一定要改掉種族刻板印象
那是中國偉人耶，繼續
我們找到卡特蓮娜丹布羅斯基
等等，母的？
對
你真的找個母的？
她做過蘇聯秘密警察
關在勞改營時，生吞活剝了獄友
好吧『臭俄後』
臭俄後和臭B王在同一隊？
行不通的
我不是在建議你，王八蛋
快去準備服裝，順便把人叫下來！
唉…
哈維爾，謝謝
我不能沒有你
你就像我唯一的親人
安啦，老弟，我會永遠罩著你
我是反派蝙蝠俠，你就是老管家了
你說我是你的老管家？
對啊，這不算是稱讚嗎？
抱歉，我的錯
夜晚通常沒什麼動靜
我和暗夜騷貨倒是會做些運動
超級英雄最常做的就是巡邏
但大家還是擠破頭想加入
這次招募新血
再不邀請陶德，好像不夠朋友
別偷看，你們會壞事
你…們…看…
穿這樣怎麼幹架？
褲子緊到青蛙眼都出來了
什麼青蛙眼？
-宅男版的激凸  -什麼?
我對這些名字不予置評
『打爆王』、『屌爆人』
-屌爆博士？  -對
老實說，有點…延伸的感覺
我來翻譯一下
你不能直接抄襲戴夫的假名，吹棒人
了…
呃…
等一下，我想到了
有了
『爆屌俠』
在開玩笑嗎？
馬堤你這王八蛋
我知道你為什麼不回我簡訊
我不是笨蛋
你確定？舔菊人俠
-去你媽的  -陶德…
不，干你娘
我會找到自己的隊友
陶德別走
陶德說的對，我們是王八蛋
但其實
我只想找明蒂進來…
…可是她忙著不當超級英雄
明蒂下來，他到了
第一次的約會，感覺如何？
我想起大老霸第一次派我去毒窟
身上只有一把小刀
我開始緊張了
做你自己就好，讓我來擔心
別擔心，我不用動手就可以殺了他
良心建議，別拿這個當開場白
謝謝你願意跟我約會
老實說…
我想不到其他方法阻止你奪命連環扣
-謝謝  -不客氣
我們要去哪裏？
參加派對
派對辦在荒郊野外？
酒桶派對不都這樣嗎？
我們大概是第一個到
這哪是辦派對的地方，傻瓜
棄屍地點倒是真的
你有問題嗎？
對不起
我會正常一點
你看起來人很好
現在呢？
來親熱吧？
別傻了
賽門，躲到車裏面
立刻！
你來了
布魯克？
這…是要幫你慶祝
慶祝？
你是一個大衰鬼
而我們排擠衰鬼
可憐的明蒂，怎麼樣啊？
帥哥覺得你很特別
邀請你參加人生第一場派對
你會第一次喝啤酒
第一次接吻？
醒一醒吧，你普通到不行
杠上我，吃不完兜著走
約會被甩了
派對在我家！
真可憐
賽門，載我們去
戴夫？
嚇死我了！明蒂？
天呀，你怎麼了？
我只是…想見我的羅賓
你沒事吧？
別哭
我不曉得該怎麼辦
那些女生，她們…
她們真邪惡
這就是高中，很快就過了
你應該回到現實世界，把世界變得更好
戴夫，我做不到
我了，你答應過爸爸
但爸爸不在了
這是你的人生，你自己要過
我明天要怎麼面對她們？
超丟臉的
怎魔會？
你聰明、漂亮、幽默
你是最堅強的人，沒有做不到的事
而且你是超殺女
戴著面具也沒差
反正那就是你
我該怎麼做？割斷她們的舌頭？
不！當然不行
嚇到你了
運用你的優勢打敗她們
做你自己就好
如果想讓人緣變好
就要考慮兩件事，性與錄影帶
蘿伊，不用聽那些恐龍妹吹牛
我可以這麼辣，你也可以
這是失蹤的毒梟給的見面禮
學我們穿衣服
不一定有我們的氣質
我穿什麼衣服並不重要
我是超級英雄，那就是我
隨便你，神鮑大俠
繼續演吧
是嗎？
你這個做作女
骨子裏是惡毒的死八婆
雞巴程度和社會敗類有得拼
你要聽實話嗎，明蒂？
在現實世界我贏定了
我會考上好大學，嫁個好老公
生個可愛北鼻
到巴黎度假，還有保姆代勞
我的人生棒透了，你的人生爛斃了
還有，不管你穿得多騷
男生都不想親你那一張臭嘴
我要是你早就割腕自殺了
再多看你一秒
我就會倒胃口
-說的好  -活該
那是什麼？智障手機？
詞窮了要搬救兵？
不瞞你說
這是我爸從國防部弄來的
本來用在場控，但效果太猛了
它會發射電波，讓人嘔吐腹瀉
我爸叫它『嘔吐棒』
要不是你爸遇到詐騙集團
就是你在做夢，親愛的
因為我們感覺超良好
就快了
哇…哩…咧…
別弄我，求求你，你贏了
我不想贏，我只是想把世界變好
爸？
在家嗎？爸？
我輪夜班賺學費，你卻在搞這個？
原來你都在變裝打架？
這棍子竟然還有血跡
你來我房間幹什麼？
我來找毒品
我擔心你
你可以放心了
我更擔心了
嗑藥還好一些
這太…瘋狂了
我還好吧
跟你的同夥比起來？
不，他們都是超級英雄
那是漫畫
真實世界是要負責任的
你何時才會長大？
我永遠不要變成你這樣
我戴面具不是因為感到羞恥
不像你
什麼意思？
休假只會練腹肌
幹嗎這樣？只為了學別人？
渾渾噩噩又過了幾年？
爸，你的人生沒有意義
你死了有誰會知道？
你要去哪裏？
離家出走，長大會做的事
他有說為什麼想見我嗎？
你叔叔拉夫打來，我也沒多問
只要他
克裏斯，別慌，不會有事的
過得怎樣？
很好，拉夫叔叔
聽我說，你爸過世以後
情況變得一團糟
我一直想讓整個家族回歸正軌
他們在錄音
我知道，隨他們
典獄長是我的人，專心聽我說
玩玩是沒關係
但幹嘛僱用一票職業殺手
哈維爾早該告訴你的
我心意已決
我要屌爆俠為他的行為付出代價
你還是忘了吧
你最好別淌渾水
你不像我或你爸，你…
比較特別
我不會聽你的
我知道我是誰了
喔，是嗎？
你是誰？
臭B王
你自以為是狠角色，是嗎？
我來告訴你什麼是真正的壞胚子
喂？
哈維爾沒事吧？
怎麼了？
你幹嘛打別人的手機？
手機又掉到馬桶了？
沒事吧？
謝謝你教我這些，我很需要
未來會很有用
別干蠢事，克裏斯
暫時避個風頭，念大學做什麼都好
何必呢？該學的你都教了
你看
快狠準，小鬼們想出超殺的隊徽
怎麼啦？聽到什麼嗎？
我們去看看，來！
有人嗎？
什麼都沒有
冷靜了再來找我，你瘋瘋的
真好奇你在煩什麼
我知道，因為今晚是你的死期
女士優先
你不會射我的
你是超級英雄
樂於助人，不會傷人
只有超級壞蛋才會做
我們軍團的名字是…
萬毒巨掰
嗨
跟你的頭一樣空
耶!
一定很痛吧
我調查過你，星條旗上校
你就是塞爾貝托裏尼吧？
『重生』以前還幫我爸做過事情
我以前都跟鱉三一起混
你有想過會這麼死嗎？
穿得像智障一樣
你又是誰？
臭B王！
我來幹掉屌爆俠，不只是斃了他
還要毀了他所愛的一切
掀了這個鬼地方
『米蘭達史瓦德洛』？
她是誰？隊裏的野女人？
暗夜騷貨…貼著屌爆俠有夠緊
看來男人有新的洩慾工具了
要我殺了這隻狗嗎？
這隻狗？你嘛幫幫忙，我沒那麼邪惡
割下他的頭
不餓嗎？我餓死了，快點
可以叫披薩嗎？
有披薩吃嘍
別急，先殺了你再說
正義…
永存
布魯克林區一位居民昨晚遭到斬首
根據推特資料，有一個人…
自稱是全世界第一個超級壞蛋
我說過別看電視，忘記你被禁足了？
我是答應過你…
但我不可能一直裝成別人
我看到邪惡就無法坐視不管
你對那些女人太殘忍了
-你差點害死她們  -我是可以
最後只是讓她們回家狂瀉
真可惜
一心只想著報復，有害身心健康
這種事情再不交給我們警察處理
我就真的救不了你
你會像你爸一樣
無法過正常生活
他們砍了那個人的頭
誰來阻止他們？
屌爆俠？還是你？
給我回房間做功課
馬上！
我們合簽一張慰問卡送給上校姐姐
每人出五塊合買一束花好不好？
你有看到臭B王的推特頁嗎？
幹嘛提到他？
我不知道，但他膽子超大
一直吹噓是他殺了星條旗上校
找得到他嗎？
我試過了，他把IP隱藏起來了
我們來開戰吧
很多人想聲援我們
這可不是西城故事
我們不是來混黑道的…
我們是來幫助別人的…
雪倫說的對，這個應該交給警察處理
以後最好團體行動
臭B王說，上校的死只是開始
有人見到暗夜騷貨嗎？
你確定她是一掛的？
這個笨蛋在她的粉絲專頁
說自己和屌爆俠正在交往
我很確定就是她
早安，暗夜騷貨！
嘿
她覺得樓上比較適合開趴
開趴羅
她關了門
別怕，親愛的，我不會殺你
我要你傳話給你的男朋友
來嘛
放開我！
寶貝，你用過超級英雄的雞巴
這次讓你試試看超級壞蛋的屌
可惡
怎麼了？
你在幹嘛？
快啊！
算了，我沒興致
大概是惡屌不舉吧
把她…打成豬頭！
條子來了
留給臭俄後
她時薪是我們的十倍
一週五萬，生活費另計
小心！
哇咧!
快倒車！
別動！
五萬，值回票價
他們幹嘛倒車？
為什麼有除草機？
哇咧!
增派警力，八個掛了
是十個啦
快走！
幫我打廣告，邪惡軍團蓄勢待發
歡迎精神失常、坐過牢的共襄盛舉
大家一定都會搶著來
他們就這樣消失了？
換上便服
就沒人認得出來
大家聽我說！
我們有所有變裝怪客的IP位址
全國執法機關
將會一舉逮捕他們
怎魔會有屌爆俠？
他們是做社區服務
我不管，變裝的全部給我抓起來
今晚就要做個了結
大家都說警方那天晚上執法過當
但平心而論
警方根本不在乎什麼是正港的英雄
只要我們撿垃圾
或扶老婦人過馬路
但這次出了大代志
我們頓時成了社會罪惡的代名詞
別動！
爸警告過我真實世界是要負責任的
警察來的時候他肯定覺得自己料事如神
這小子，到底幹了什麼事？
警察，開門
嘿
嗨
是我，屌爆俠
哇
本人還真可愛
我很抱歉你發生這種事
不甘你的事
是我自找的
我們要找到這些王八蛋，為你報仇
有意義嗎？
英雄或約會
對我們來說是一樣的虛假
我們甚至不知道彼此的姓名
是該回歸現實的時候了
我以為我們都想讓世界變得更好
怎麼反而變得更糟？
或許暗夜騷貨說的對…
我爸也說中了
我是指，情勢失控了
我是該回家
跟爸爸道歉了吧
爸？
那是我爸
你爸是屌爆俠？
他剛剛承認了
你不懂，他只是為了保護我
爸！
-明蒂？  -戴夫？
我爸被捕了
警方以為他是屌爆俠
你可以跟馬庫斯說一聲嗎？
-我被禁足了  -所以呢？
我管不了
-等一下  -我無能為力
明蒂，你有在聽嗎？
我要掛了
抱歉，戴夫
明蒂，別掛
你到底在想什麼？
我才要問你
你怎麼可以騙他們？
我不會讓你坐牢的
你應該讓我自行承擔後果
我以為你希望我長大
你當了爸媽就會懂的
我要跟他們說實話
不，事情只會愈來愈糟
律師說
明天就可以回家
罪名都不成立
外面有很多人想殺屌爆俠
這裏有警察看著
關在這裏才是最安全的
我不知道你怎麼惹到這些麻煩，但…
你要答應我別再穿那套衣服
聽到了嗎？
我答應你
這個大本營大家都說贊！
聽起來有點老派
黑白講
你的鯊魚快掛了
大概是水的問題
搞什麼，伊亞？
你放心，鯊魚喜歡躺在水槽底部
這是它們融入環境的方式
別呼嚨我
你說兩天就會完工
結果連廁所都沒有
你放心
那幾袋垃圾是啥？
做炸彈用的
不摧毀整座城市就不算超級壞蛋
沒用的，化學肥料才行
我什麼事情都要自己來嗎？
還不去弄!
放輕鬆，一切會照計劃進行
但可惜沒有，懂嗎？
那個替死鬼不是屌爆俠
我看過他本人，就跟我同年紀
那個人都可以當他爸了
沒錯
不好意思，你哪位？
我是來加入你的軍團的
歡迎，肛溫，感謝你為邪惡而戰
這裏是核心成員VIP專區
我只是覺得你很好笑
因為他就是屌爆俠的爸爸
誰？
萊佐斯基先生，屌爆俠他爸
少來了！
真的，別告訴其他人
我不會
但是你剛取得了VIP永久會員身份
找位置坐
給他一杯星冰樂…
再叫這個豬頭去工作
知道了
過來
有事嗎？
臭B王要我們一起合照
安啦，我爸是一流的律師
不然我在監獄
肯定會被肛肛好
怪了，克裏斯達米柯竟然傳照片給我
赤霧俠？他怎麼樣了？
到底是什麼？
戴夫，怎麼了？
我後來幾天渾渾噩噩
無論我跟警方怎麼描述克裏斯…
他們就是找不到人
警察也來參加我爸的葬禮
不是出於尊重
而是想避免恐怖事件
我爸是個好人
他總是努力讓我過好日子
我竟然跟他說，他死了沒人會知道
我愛你，哥們
我也愛你，爸
你們來了
我們想幫你追查克裏斯這個人渣
但我們還在假釋期
沒關係
我並不想復仇
我最後答應爸爸不再變裝
我說到做到
這是你起的頭
現在由我結束
很抱歉，你會恨我見死不救嗎？
不，一點也不
你是對的，你退出了
如果我也退出，我爸就不會死
我只怪我自己
大開殺戒！
趴下！
明蒂！
散開！
壓低身體！
過來！
哇-哩-咧!
去抓他！
把貨車開過來！
快點！
明蒂？
明蒂！
把這個穿上
門都沒有
你傷不了我的
你確定？
哇!咧!
開戰吧，死雜碎
車頂有個女孩！
她還在
-我甩掉她了  -去確認
出去搞定！
把頭移開
停車，陰毛臉
我們知道克裏斯就是臭B王
他躲在哪裏？
舔我的老二
不說就讓你舔自己的
殺了我吧，小賤人
你沒有辦法逼我說的
住手，時機不對，這是我爸的葬禮
戴夫，你爸很愛你
就像我爸很愛我，我知道很痛苦
但或許這是成為超級英雄的意義
承受痛苦，化悲憤為力量
正義的力量
還記得你說過的話嗎？
這是你的人生，你自己要過
幫我找鉗子，我要讓他吸自己的老二
說真的？
-喂？  -馬庫斯？
怎麼了？你沒事吧？
我很好
我們知道臭B王躲在哪裏
他組了邪惡軍團，正在製作炸彈
他想炸了這個城市
你答應過我
我知道你把我當成小女孩
但我不是，從來都不是
你說得對
大老霸確實剝奪我的童年
但我不覺得是壞事
他教我的本領
我說什麼也無法忘記
我不用浪費四年
尋找自我
因為我早就知道
我是超殺女
我貼了地址，他們會來嗎？
克裏斯有一票人耶
他們一輩子就等著這個機會，會來的
你沒事吧？
什麼？沒事，我很好
這個
拿著
用這個不符合我的行事風格
戴夫，這不是漫畫
今晚會有人死的
我爸都會做好萬全準備
你呢？
嗯
準備好了
他們應該到了吧！
絕對死了
網路上說要用淡水養鯊魚
它只是餓了，餵它東西吃
幹嘛看著我？
我們要馬上開始
沒錯，我為你們這群人準備了一場秀
臭B王，臭B王…
夠了，派對咖！
我們要一起殺了屌爆俠
第一個超級英雄
我們要把他碎屍萬段
餵飽這只鎚頭鯊
再把影片上傳，說到做到！
這是開玩笑吧？
臭B王說到做到
不只這樣，我會發給每個人…
派對良伴甲烷炸彈！
我們要讓世界大亂!
這才叫邪惡
我們才是社會菁英…
今晚要鬧翻這座城市，否則我就不叫…
克裏斯達米柯!
那不是我的名字！
對，那不是，你的本名是小孬孬
噢，老天爺真幫我
你真的那麼腦殘？
兩個人也想找我們單挑
真的那麼想死？
不…
所以我們還撂人來
怎麼了，克裏斯？閃尿了？
對，等你幫我舔乾淨
你要為我爸的死付出代價
你爸？你用火箭筒殺了我爸
噢!
想死了嗎，小屁孩？
如果繼續看你的屎臉，我可能很想死
克裏斯！
壓住他，我想看他多有能耐
你們真是夠了！
幹得好，親愛的
就這樣？
不，還有我的零重力裝置
瞎掰
是真的
沒事吧？
沒事，謝謝，爆屌俠
幹得好
天啊,你還真孬
沒本是裝什麼英雄
我們想要主持正義
才怪，一般人只想中樂透
只想睡正妹
憑那根針也想殺我？
你會錯意了
這是腎上腺素，賤貨
幹嘛？偷吃步？
你欠上校的
啊!
這是你欠暗夜騷貨的
這是你欠我爸的
你想幹什麼？
救你這個靠爸族!
不！
我才不要，我寧願死！
你還當真？這不是漫畫，這是人生！
你死了就一了百了，沒有續集
你造的孽，你起的頭！
讓我來終結這一切
我會受後世傳頌，就像邪惡耶穌
等一下！
我還活著
戴夫，讓你失望了
這感覺難以言喻
克裏斯達米柯，死了
他自稱的邪惡軍團，敗了
但世界真的有變好嗎？
還是說僅僅收拾了…
這套服裝所製造的問題
警察快來了
他們會搞定那些壞蛋
大家最好趁機溜走
我們辦到了
我靠
別說髒話
你說的對，扮英雄就要有英雄的樣子
他會以你為榮，戴夫
他會以大家為榮
這是最後一次了吧？
結束了
最後一次吶喊，來吧
你呢，超殺女？要來嗎？
沒差
正義永存！
謝謝你載我回家
學校見
我要離開紐約，戴夫
我不能回家，我不想馬庫斯難做人
為什麼？他不會逮捕你的
你救了整座城市
我還拿警用手槍殺了六個人
我用的是私行
你不能走，大家需要你
-他們有你就夠了  -明蒂…
我比不上你
當英雄不一定要很猛，戴夫
只要有勇氣就夠了
這是？
我的初吻
好好做人
不然就把你屁股從嘴裏扯出來
明蒂離開以後
我總算看清方向
這個世界總有人…
想當超級英雄
但總有終結的一刻
超級英雄無法存在於真實世界
原因只有一個
真實世界只需要正港的英雄
不是穿潛水服的變裝癖
而是真正屌爆的英雄們
哈羅？
拜託！別走
別走！
那有人嗎？
哈羅？
請給我一些幫助！
鯊魚咬掉了我的雞雞，這他媽的叫我怎麼喝水？
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人